Nikolai Dorofeev

System Analyst

IT specialist of experience in wide range of technologies. Worked with different ecosystems: JavaScript, Node.js, Python, Java, C#. Integrated systems via REST API, SOAP, gRPC, RabbitMQ. Took lead role in creation of documentation for Kubernetes-based microservices solution.



Languages

- English: Upper-Intermediate
- · Russian: Native

Skills

Security



Design patterns

Work Experience

Fullstack Developer Exactpro (Georgia)

Jul 2022 - Present (11 months)

- Led development of a easy-to-deploy and easy-to-update docs web toolkit package based on **Nuxt.js** and **Tailwind CSS**
- Configured CI/CD pipelines for publishing static websites and npm packages via GitHub actions, GitLab CI
- Developed #1 architecture for providing traceability of digital assets between Blockchains for Swift Hackathon 2022
- · Mentored junior specialists and technical writers

Fullstack Developer Exactpro

Jul 2021 - Jul 2022 (1 year)

- Developed a custom website template for documentation with features for technical writers using Gridsome (Vue.js + GraphQL)
- Developed demonstration Python and Kotlin modules for th2 complex Kubernetes-based microservices framework with gRPC and RabbitMQ communication
- Configured CI/CD pipelines for building and publishing static websites via GitHub actions and Jenkins
- Wrote clear and easy-to-understand documentation for complex Kubernetesbased microservices framework

Projects

- <u>tradeb0t</u>: im Trading software with high integration possibilities
- th2-cli: CLI for managing th2 infrastructure in Kubernetes cluster
- tweetst0rm: 🐔 Simple app that uses GPT-3 for generating tweets.

Certificates

- Enterprise Patterns (<u>foxminded.ua</u>, May 2023): <u>Course Page</u>, <u>Certificate</u>, <u>Verify</u>
 <u>Certificate</u>
- Architecting With Google Kubernetes Engine (Coursera, Oct 2021): Certificate
- Fundamentals Of Digital Marketing (<u>Google Digital Garage</u>, Jul 2021):
 Certificate

Education

Information Systems And Technologies <u>Tomsk Polytechnic University</u> Sep 2018 - Jul 2022 (3 years 10 months)

Get a bachelor's degree in Information Systems and Technology in Business.